(Sheldon:)opening the freezer and going,
"Aw, no strawberry."
(Penny:)What about the girl
behind the counter?
(Sheldon:)Hmm? Well, she spends
her whole day scooping.
(Sheldon:)One arm's probably
bigger than the other.
(Penny:)Is it possible you might not
actually want to meet someone?
(Sheldon:)You are truly wise.
(Penny:)Thank you.
(Sheldon:)I'd say
(Sheldon:)wise beyond your years,
but you're getting up there.
(Penny:)All right.
(Penny:)Come on. What is really
going on with you?
(Sheldon:)Penny, I am going
to tell you a story
(Sheldon:)that I've never told anyone.
(Penny:)All right.
(Sheldon:)I was 13 years old,
(Sheldon:)and on spring break
from college.
(Penny:)Not relating. Go on.
(Sheldon:)I came home early because they
ran out of math to teach me.
(Penny:)Oh, now I'm with ya. Okay.
(Sheldon:)My mother was at bible study.
(Sheldon:)I walked in the house
expecting to find it empty,
(Sheldon:)and I heard a sound coming
from my parents' bedroom.